{
    "questions": [
      {
        "number": 1,
        "question": "How many sub-books are there in the Book of Mormon?",
        "answers": [
          "12",
          "15",
          "18",
          "20"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2   
      },
      {
        "number": 2,
        "question": "What was the name of the mountain to which the brother of Jared said 'Remove â€” and it was removed?'",
        "answers": [
          "Zerin",
          "Serphim",
          "Jershap",
          "Shimrod"
          
        
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
      },
      {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "What noun is used as a verb in the Book of Mormon?",
        "answers": [
          "gladden",
          "happying",
          "excited",
          "joyed"
          
        ],
        "correct_answer": 4
      },
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "Ammon defended the flocks after being in the service of the king how long?",
        "answers": [
          "3 days",
          "3 weekends",
          "3 weeks",
          "3 years"
          
    
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
      },
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "Who was one of the 12 Nephite disciples?",
        "answers": [
          "Jonas",
          "Jonah",
          "Judas",
          "Judah"
          
          
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
      },
      {
        "number": 6,
        "question": "Which adverb is used in the Book of Mormon?",
        "answers": [
          "gracefully",
          "suspiciously",
          "vicariously",
          "circumspectly"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 4
      },
      {
        "number": 7,
        "question": "What farewell phrase is used in the Book of Mormon?",
        "answers": [
          "adios",
          "goodbye",
          "ciao",
          "adieu"
          
    
        ],
        "correct_answer": 4
      },
     
      {
        "number": 8,
        "question": "Who was NOT one of the Eight Witnesses ?",
        "answers": [
          "Hiram",
          "Hyrum",
          "David",
          "Joseph"
         
        ],
        "correct_answer": 3
      },
      {
        "number": 9,
        "question": "What term is used in the Book of Mormon?",
        "answers": [
          "lagoon",
          "bay",
          "gulf",
          "ocean"
         
        ],
        "correct_answer": 3
      },
      {
        "number": 10,
        "question": "What phrase is found in the Book of Mormon ?",
        "answers": [
          "all-searching eye",
          "ring of God",
          "lips of the Lord",
          "arm of wrath"
         
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
      }
    ]
  }